(Howard:)Boy, seems like forever since
the four of us have been out to eat.
You know, just the guys.
Oh, God. Yes, we get it.
You have a girlfriend now.
(Howard:)-A little jealous, are we?
-No, I'm not jealous.
All right, I'd kill a hobo if it would
get me laid. Now, can we order?
(Sheldon:)Oh, dear Lord, they redid the menu.
(Leonard:)So what? It's the same food.
(Sheldon:)Oh, is it? Look at this.
(Sheldon:)General Tso's Chicken
is no longer listed under "specialties."
It's now under "chicken."
(Raj:)-So?
-Yes, General Tso.
Not "Tso" the chicken,
"so" the question.
(Raj:)-So?
-So why is it no longer a specialty?
(Sheldon:)Did the chef lose confidence
in the dish or himself?
(Sheldon:)And look over here.
"Shrimp in mobster sauce."
(Sheldon:)What is mobster sauce?